Music from the Bob Hope Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music from Identified Films, Television Programs and Public Appearances, 1953-1997 (Box 1-54, 82-90, 95-112, 117-121)
  - 1994: Bob and Dolores Hope: Hope's for the holidays (recording), Scores and parts; Titles: Christmas eve; Christmas time is here; Deck the halls/jingle bells; Do you hear what I hear?; Have yourself a merry little Christmas; Home; I'll be home for Christmas; Jesus was born today; Snowbound; A time to be jolly (Box-folder 54/12; 88/5; 120/1-9)
  - 1995: Now and then (Dolores Hope recording), Scores and parts; Titles: But beautiful; Come in from the rain; Here's that rainy day/I'm always chasing rainbows; It amazes me; It could happen to you; Just the way you are; You do something/I've got you under my skin (Box-folder 89/6-8; 90/1-4)
  - 1995: Somewhere in time: the songs and spirit of World War II (Dolores Hope recording), Scores and parts; Titles: Craziest dream; I'll walk alone; I'm beginning to see the light; I've heard that song before; It had to be you; The last time I saw Paris; No love, no lovin'; Taking a chance on love; Waiting for the train to come in; We'll meet again; You'd be so nice to come home to (Box-folder 90/5-11; 121/1-5)
  - 1997: That's love (Dolores Hope recording), Scores and parts; Titles: I only have eyes for you; That's love; Why can't you behave (Box-folder 90/12; 121/6-7)
- Music from Unidentified Sources, 1932-1992 (Box 55-81, 91-94, 113-116, 122)
  Manuscript scores, parts, lead sheets, and lyric sheets for unidentified films, television programs, and public appearances. Part sets are assumed to be complete unless otherwise noted.
  Arranged alphabetically by title of work.
  - 1980 Hope opening montage (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 91/1)
  - Abdul (1985 February 1), Scores and parts (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Aerobics (1985 February 1), Scores and parts (Box-folder 55/2)
  - Ain't misbehavin' (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Air Force (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Alcatraz scene (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 55/5)
  - All I need is the girl (undated), Score and parts; For Bob Hope and Bing Crosby (Box-folder 55/6)
  - All the way (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 55/7)
  - All of me (undated), Published arrangements; Arranged by Joe Leahy and Johnny Warrington (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Am I in love? (undated), Lead sheet (Box-folder 56/1)
  - Applause (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Are you havin' any fun? (undated), Score, parts, and published arrangement (Box-folder 56/3)
  - The Army Air Corps (undated), Published arrangement (Box-folder 56/4)
  - As time goes by (stingers and play-off) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Baby, I need you (undated), Lead sheets, lyric sheets (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Baby, that's me without you (undated), Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Bad, bad Leroy Brown (undated), Published score and parts (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Be anything (undated), Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Best friend (undated), Lead sheets; guitar parts; Inscribed: Dolores Hope (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Bing's spin (transition music) (undated), Lead sheets; guitar parts (Box-folder 91/2)
  - Blue of the night (play-on, play-off, underscore) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 91/3-4; 113/1)
  - Blues (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Bob and Sammy (duet) (undated), Scores and parts; Titles: Side by side; Me and my shadow (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Bonanza (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 91/5; 113/2)
  - Boxer's rebellion (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Breaker-breaker of my heart (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Brenda and Cobina (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/5)
  - Bumpkin (play-on) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/6)
  - Button up your overcoat (1991), Scores and parts (Box-folder 57/7)
  - Buttons and bows (undated), Scores and parts; Various arrangements (Box-folder 58/1)
  - By the light of the silvery moon (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 58/2)
  - Captain Custard (play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 91/6)
  - Carioca (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 58/3)
  - The challenge (undated), Conductor's score; Inscribed: Jayne Mansfield (Box-folder 58/4)
  - Charo (play-on, play-off) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 58/5)
  - Cheers (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Chinese overcoat (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Choir medley (1987), Scores and parts; Titles: Battle hymn of the Republic; Smile (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Christmas theme button (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Circus extravaganza (undated), Published parts (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Circus Maximus (undated), Published parts (Box-folder 59/6)
  - City lady country girl (undated), Lead sheet (Box-folder 59/7)
  - Clock effect (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Colonial (play-on, play-off) (undated), Conductor's score; Inscribed: Jayne Mansfield (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Colonel Bogey march (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 113/3)
  - Colossus of Columbia march (undated), Published parts (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Connections (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 60/4)
  - The Continental (parody) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 60/5)
  - Copter tour (1979, 1990), Score and parts (Box-folder 91/7)
  - Cottonfields (undated), Parts; Arranged by Shorty Rogers (Box-folder 60/6)
  - A couple of swells (undated), Score and parts; Duet: Bernadette Peters and Bob Hope (Box-folder 61/1)
  - The cowboys and the singers (undated), Lead sheet (Box-folder 61/2)
  - Cowpokes (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 61/3)
  - Danny boy (play on) (1985), Scores and parts (Box-folder 61/4)
  - Darn it, baby (1964), Scores and parts; Duet: multiple arrangements (Box-folder 61/5)
  - Dean Martin (play-off) (undated), Parts; Inscribed: Dean Martin show (Box-folder 62/1)
  - Deb-stars '91 (1991), Scores and parts (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Disco bells (1979), Scores and parts; Inscribed: special material - Ray Charles (Box-folder 62/3)
  - Dixie / Swanee medley (undated), Scores and parts; For Red Buttons (Box-folder 62/4)
  - Doctor "K" (undated), Scores and parts; Inscribed: Astronaut underscore (Box-folder 92/1)
  - Doggie Bowser (1990), Scores and parts; Paraphrase of "Doogie Howser" theme (Box-folder 62/5)
  - Domestic ladies (1982), Scores and parts (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Don't sit under the apple tree (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 62/7)
  - Don't worry, be happy (1989), Scores and parts; Inscribed: Never used (Box-folder 62/8)
  - Dynasty (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 63/1)
  - Easter parade (play-on) (1991), Scores and parts (Box-folder 63/2)
  - Easy to love (undated), Scores and parts; Jimmy Stewart (play-on) (Box-folder 63/3)
  - Eight to four (parody on "Working 9 to 5") (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 113/4)
  - Elegance (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 63/4)
  - Ernie Kovacs (play-on) (1976), Scores and parts; Inscribed: Bob Hope T.V. (Box-folder 92/2)
  - Fight montage theme (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Finale (undated), Scores and parts; Titles: This is only the beginning; On a wonderful day like today (Box-folder 63/6)
  - Flossie, the three faces of Bob (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 64/1)
  - Fly me to the moon (Moon hustle) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 64/2)
  - Friends (undated), Scores and parts; From the television show "Sesame Street" (Box-folder 64/3)
  - Frog legs (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 64/4)
  - The game (undated), Scores and parts; For the Dean Martin Show (Dean, Zero, Shecky, Buddy and choir) (Box-folder 64/5)
  - Gentle on my mind (undated), Scores and parts; Glen Campbell (Box-folder 114/1)
  - Gillette theme (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 64/6)
  - Global news cues (undated), Scores and parts; Titles: Hooray for Hollywood; Volga boatmen; La Marseilles; Peking duck; Hamachi (Box-folder 64/7)
  - Go get 'em (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/1)
  - God bless America (undated), Published parts (Box-folder 65/2)
  - Golden girls (play-on, play-off) (1987), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/3)
  - Goldfinger (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Gorby's greatest hits (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/5)
  - Habit / Crush medley (1986), Scores and parts; Booke Shields and Bob Hope (Box-folder 65/6)
  - Hail, Columbia (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 65/7)
  - Hail to the Chief (undated), Score and parts; Arranged by Manny Harmon (Box-folder 65/8)
  - Happy birthday (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/9)
  - Happy birthday (rock version) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 65/10)
  - Happy days are here again (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 92/3)
  - Hard to handle (tag) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/1)
  - Harpies (1983), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Hart to Hart (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/3)
  - He's funny that way (undated), Lead sheets; Inscribed: Dolores Hope (Box-folder 66/4)
  - He's gone away (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Here's Lucy [Lucille Ball theme] (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Hey there (play-on) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/7)
  - Highway to Heaven (play-on, play-off) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/8)
  - Hill Street blues (play-on) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/9)
  - Hip noses (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 92/4)
  - H.N.N. Signature (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/10)
  - Hometown (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 66/11)
  - Hope / Franklin medley (undated), Score and parts; Duet: Aretha Franklin and Bob Hope (Box-folder 67/1)
  - Hope play-offs (undated), Score and parts; Duet: Aretha Franklin and Bob Hope (Box-folder 67/2-5)
  - Hoppone tarantella (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 68/1)
  - How much is that doggie in the window (play-on) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 68/2)
  - I can't get started (1984), Score and parts (Box-folder 68/3)
  - I thought about you (undated), Lead sheet; Inscribed: Dolores Hope (Box-folder 68/4)
  - I wish I was eighteen again (undated), Scores and parts; Inscribed: George Burns (Box-folder 68/5)
  - If I could be with you (1978), Score and parts (Box-folder 69/1)
  - If my friends could see me now (parody for Holley Systems) (1978), Parts; sheet music; lyric sheets; Les Brown arrangement for Holley Distributors Awards Breakfast (Box-folder 69/2)
  - International ladies (1982), Score and parts (Box-folder 69/3)
  - Irish fling (1988), Score and parts (Box-folder 69/4)
  - Italian village (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 69/5)
  - It's a lovely day today (1992), Score and parts; Dolores Hope (Box-folder 69/6)
  - It's a small world afterall (play-on) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 69/7)
  - It's delovely (1989), Score and parts (Box-folder 70/1; 114/2)
  - It's impossible (1980), Score and parts (Box-folder 70/2)
  - It's today (undated), Parts (Box-folder 70/3)
  - I've seen that step before (1990), Score and parts (Box-folder 70/4)
  - Jingle bells (1960), Score and parts; For Peggy Lee's recording "Christmas carousel" (Box-folder 92/5)
  - Jingle bells (undated), Score and parts; For the Mel Tormé television show (Box-folder 92/6)
  - Jowls (1984), Scores and parts; Paraphrase of "Jaws" (Box-folder 70/5)
  - Juke-box boob-tube (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 70/6)
  - Jungle sketch (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 70/7)
  - Just in time (undated), Lead sheet; Inscribed: Dolores Hope (Box-folder 70/8)
  - The kiss (1982), Scores and parts (Box-folder 70/9)
  - Lese Majesty (1981), Scores and parts (Box-folder 114/3)
  - Let a smile be your umbrella (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 92/7)
  - Look for the silver lining (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 70/10)
  - Louis et Marie (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 70/11)
  - Love concoction (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/1)
  - Love nest / Christmas (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/2)
  - Lovely to look at (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts; Inscribed: Jill St. John (Box-folder 71/3)
  - Lucille Ball theme (1982, 1984), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/4)
  - Lucky McGee (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/5)
  - Lydia, the tattooed lady (parody: Lybia) (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/6; 92/8)
  - Make-up (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/7)
  - Manhattan (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 71/8)
  - La Marseilles sketch (play-on) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/1)
  - Melancholy baby (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/2)
  - Melancholy serenade (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/3)
  - Miscellaneous cues (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/4; 93/1-2; 115/1-2)
  - Miss America (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/5)
  - Moonlight becomes you (underscore) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 93/3)
  - Mountie sketch (undated), Scores and parts; Inscribed: Bob Hope Show (Box-folder 72/6)
  - Mr. Touchdown U.S.A. (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/7)
  - Mr. Wonderful (play-on) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/8)
  - Musical milestones (undated), Scores and parts; For Sammy Davis Jr. (Box-folder 93/4)
  - Mutineers (1986 November), Scores and parts (Box-folder 72/9)
  - My way (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/1)
  - Near you (play-on) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/2)
  - Nicky and Alex fanfare (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/3)
  - Odd couple theme (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 93/5)
  - Oh, you beautiful doll (play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/4)
  - Olympic documentary (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/5)
  - One Bob play-off (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/6)
  - Our love / Romeo and Juliet (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/7)
  - Outer space (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 73/8)
  - Perry Como intro "Dream along with me" (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/1)
  - Pompous entrance music (undated), Scores and parts; Paraphrase of "Pomp and circumstance" (Box-folder 74/2)
  - Pretty A.M. (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/3)
  - Radio themes overture (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/4)
  - Rah-rah cheerleaders (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/5)
  - Raindrops keep falling (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/6)
  - Ready, aim, fire (bridge) (1989), Scores and parts (Box-folder 74/7)
  - Red Buttons (play-on) (undated), Published arrangement (Box-folder 74/8)
  - Remembering (1991), Scores and parts (Box-folder 75/1)
  - Road to Morocco (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 75/2; 93/6; 122/5)
  - Rocky (underscore) (undated), Scores and parts; Note on folder: Not from the movie "Rocky" (Box-folder 75/3)
  - Russian lullaby (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 75/4)
  - Salvation (play-off) (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 94/1)
  - School daze (play-on, play-off) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 94/2)
  - Semper paratus (Coast Guard marching song) (1992 April 28), Parts (Box-folder 75/5)
  - Shadow (intro) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 94/3)
  - Sidewalks of New York (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 116/1)
  - Silent night (undated), Parts (Box-folder 75/6)
  - Silver bells (undated), Score and parts; For "Voices of Christmas" recording with Les Brown (Box-folder 75/7)
  - Silver bells (undated), Score and parts; Arranged by Frank Comstock (Box-folder 75/8)
  - Small fry (1972), Scores and parts (Box-folder 76/1)
  - Straight down the middle (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 76/2)
  - Sweet and lovely (1982), Parts (Box-folder 76/3)
  - Take me out to the ballgame (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 116/2)
  - Tartakoff fanfare (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 76/5)
  - Teamwork (finish) (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 94/4)
  - Tension cue (1984), Scores and parts (Box-folder 76/6)
  - Terror music / Peanut (play-off) (undated), Parts (Box-folder 76/4)
  - Thanks for the memories (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 77/1-6; 94/5; 116/3)
  - Thanks for the memories (1979), Scores and parts (Box-folder 122/2)
  - That's all that matters to me (1932), Sheet music; Dolores (Reade) Hope featured on cover (Box-folder 78/1)
  - Themes: Mannix; Gentle-goodnight; Star Trek; Gunsmoke (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 78/2)
  - There will never be another you (undated), Lead sheet; Inscribed: Dolores Hope (Box-folder 78/3)
  - This is all I need (1982), Parts (Box-folder 78/4)
  - This land is your land (play-on) (undated), Parts; Arranged by Dave Wolpe (Box-folder 78/5)
  - Those were the days (undated), Scores and parts; Duet: Dionne Warwick, Bob Hope; instrumental (Box-folder 78/6-7)
  - Tie a yellow ribbon (1991), Scores and parts; For Clint Black (Box-folder 79/1)
  - Time killer (1979), Scores and parts (Box-folder 94/6)
  - Tomorrow (1980), Parts (Box-folder 79/2)
  - Tonight show theme (undated), Scores and parts; Also known as "Johnny's theme" (Box-folder 79/3)
  - Tribute to teams (undated), Scores and parts; Duet (Box-folder 79/4)
  - The two of us (undated), Scores and parts; Duet (Box-folder 79/5)
  - Unchained melody (1990), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/1)
  - Up, up and away (1983 September), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/2)
  - Utility transition (1985), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/3)
  - Vodka boatman (undated), Parts (Box-folder 80/4)
  - Walk of fame (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/5)
  - Walton's theme (1974), Score and parts; 1974 Emmy Awards (Box-folder 80/6)
  - Watch the birdie (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 116/4)
  - We're in the money (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/7; 116/5)
  - Whispering / Charleston (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 80/8)
  - Whatta martini (undated), Scores and parts, (2 measure transition) (Box-folder 94/7)
  - Who taught us everything (undated), Parts; Duet for Ben Vereen and Bob Hope (Box-folder 81/1)
  - Yesterdays (underscore) (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 116/6)
  - Yeth, thir! (1990), Scores and parts (Box-folder 81/2)
  - You gotta have heart (undated), Score and parts; Vocal and instrumental versions (Box-folder 81/3)
  - You oughta be in pictures (play-on, play-off) (undated), Score and parts (Box-folder 94/8)
  - You're the top (1980), Scores and parts (Box-folder 81/4)
  - You've brought a new kind of love (undated), Scores and parts (Box-folder 94/9)